This catsuit has a zipper in such an unusual place I've not seen it before.
Okay in a lack of better words I'm going to call this a butt flap because the zipper
here is across the booty and I'm going to try it on. I put it on my wish list
when I saw this and someone bought it and thanks a lot and if you want to see
other cool stuff in my videos check out my wish list but I'm going to open the
zipper today while I'm wearing a catsuit so safety first and I will change
okay let's try it on
So far so good I'd say.
Let me check.
This is size small and I'm going to put on some shoes real quick to complete the look.
Okay, put on some shoes and by the way, I found out the original designer of this
um, yeah, design is Rick Owens and normally this catsuit is made of leather, so if you want to
gift it to me, feel free to write me. Anyway, this here is kind of wet look and now we're going to
the interesting part. I'm going to open this butt flap, I don't know, butt zipper. Oh, by the way,
YouTube this is for scientific reasons please don't delete my account.
Like what? This feels so weird to be honest. I mean I think it is that you can
go to the toilet without undressing completely. Let's maybe check it out.
Well, if I am imagining sitting on a toilet right now, this is totally working.
It does feel so weird though.
But I mean, to normal people going to the toilet and having a catsuit with a cross zipper
probably also feels weird.
So I'm just going to do it.
But as you can see, it would totally be possible.
It's a bit weird.
Oh and getting up is a bit more complicated because now it got stuck here on my back.
Wait.
Okay, so you have to pull it up and down.
Or you can get up and close it again.
I mean what are the options for catsuits?
there is no crotch zipper or something like this you have to undress completely
when you go to the toilet and sit basically naked on the loo which does
feel weird and if you have a crotch zipper you're at least completely dressed but
with this option your butt is hanging out I don't know it's also a bit weird
it does work it's practical it's more practical than no zipper of course I
think I still prefer a crotch zipper because yeah there are no parts of you
hanging out imagine being a guy and wearing this catsuit anyway I think in
general it's a nice fitting catsuit I like the biker style here with the
asymmetrical zipper it's definitely something I didn't see before
Did you see other weird zippers and I don't know clothing pieces you thought
Well, what's that for or how does that work? Leave a comment down below
tell me about it, maybe I can do another video about something like that and
If you want to see more behind the scenes and more photo sets check out my patreon and I will see you in the next video
Thanks for joining today. Have a nice day. Bye